caboki.com 2016-06-11

# Caboki.com Privacy Policy

**Effective: January 10, 2016**

We will never share, sell, barter, or rent your personal information such as your email address to any third party other than as disclosed within this privacy policy.

Caboki LLC ("Caboki") values the protection of individual privacy. This privacy policy sets forth Caboki's privacy policy for the site, and governs the manner in which we collect, use, maintain and disclose information collected from our users. By using our site [www.caboki.com](http://www.caboki.com/index.html), you agree to be bound by this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use the site.

Caboki has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@caboki.com](mailto:privacy@caboki.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

## How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you request free sample or when you make a purchase. Like most Web sites, Caboki.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit.

## The Types of Personal Information We Collect and How We Use It

During registration you are required to give us your name, email address and a password. We use this information to create your account, send you monthly newsletters which you may opt-out of at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of each communication or by logging into your account and deselecting the box, and contact you about the services in which you have expressed interest.

If you purchase a product from us, we request certain personal information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Based upon the personal information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your account information and a newsletter sign up verification email. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of the referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [privacy@caboki.com](mailto:privacy@caboki.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

Like other web sites, we collect information to enhance your visit. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used to enhance user experience. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive).

## Who We May Share Your Information With

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order, processing your payment, or offering customer services. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, in response to a court order, at other times when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

## Children

Caboki.com does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13.

## Access to Personal Information

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete inaccuracies, or request deletion of your account by making the change within the "my account" section of the site or by emailing us at [privacy@caboki.com](mailto:privacy@caboki.com). We will respond to your access request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active of as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@caboki.com](mailto:privacy@caboki.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Customer Reviews

We post customer reviews/video reviews on our Web site which may contain personal information. We do obtain the customer’s consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial/video. To request removal of your personal information or video from our reviews, contact us at [privacy@caboki.com](mailto:privacy@caboki.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Surveys

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

We use this information Describe fully how the data collected is to be used, e.g., to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic or personalize the site (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys), to send participants an email newsletter.

We use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests; that company is prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. Use the latter disclosure only if your service-provider contracts expressly prohibit this. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

## Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by [www.caboki.com](http://www.caboki.com/index.html) and our partners specify type e.g. marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers specify type e.g. online customer support provider, etc. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

## Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

## Flash LSO

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash to collect and store information. To manage Flash LSOs please click here:

<http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

## Behavioral Targeting/ Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receicve it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

## Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personal information.

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Web site.

## Changes to this Policy

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contact Us:

Caboki LLC  
3 Corporate Drive  
Cranbury, NJ 08512 USA  
Email: privacy@caboki.com
